

SKILLS

I have experience working with teams to brainstorm and whiteboard concepts. I can create wireframes at varying levels of fidelity, and enjoy prototyping ideas. I have some front-end coding experience, and enjoy working with devs to build out designs. I have expertise in photography, a lifelong passion of mine. I have worked in multidisciplinary teams that included, among others, executives, designers, developers, & marketers.

Software that I'm familiar with:

- Xd
- Sketch
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- InDesign
- Lightroom
- Keynote
- HTML & CSS
- Office 365 / G Suite
- * I have worked with many different tools and frameworks - to avoid a full laundry-list, I've listed a few favorites above. If you use a different tool that works well in your workflow, I'd be happy to learn it.

EXPERIENCE

Oct 2018 - Present

Authentic Vacations

Head of IT

- Work cross-functionally with product, operations, marketing, sales, and development teams to define current and future priorities, capitalize on efficiencies and ensure consistency in approach and delivery.
- Streamline product development functions by developing and implementing process and task management protocols.
- Identify technical issues and manage on-site support, providing the first line of support for local and remote issues.
- Strategically scale web technology solutions for the company (knowledge base, help desk, etc.)
- Manage multiple facets of Property/Database Management Systems.
- Find ways to automate, streamline, and improve the employee experience relating to IT and operations.
- Software & Hardware installation, maintenance, and support

Sept 2017 - Present

Authentic Vacations

Product Designer & Content Coordinator

- Create initial wireframes and high-fidelity mockups for new B2C and B2B experiences
- Design marketing collateral including brochures, flyers, social media graphics, trade show & office signage
- Storyboard, organize, & create marketing videos to enhance brand image
- Create responsive web pages that detailed company services & promotions
- Develop and recommend workflows & styleguides for web content development, implementation, and maintenance
- Collaborate with the team of developers to integrate content with website design and function for optimum communication
- Support the wider marketing team in implementing company SEO plans and best practices
- Help oversee website design and social media to ensure content is effective, relevant, and professional

EDUCATION

2011 - 2015

Santa Rosa Junior College

Humanities / Humanistic Studies